Harvard University. Corporation. Records of land and property owned by Harvard University, 1643-1835: an inventory
Records of land and property owned by Harvard University, 1643-1835
- XX. Other lands, 1647-1830, .30 cubic feet (18 legal folders and 6 oversize folders)
  - Manuscript copy of Thomas H. Darling’s deed for land in Concord, Lincoln, and Bedford, May 4, 1830, UAI 15.750 Box 7, Folder 101
Formerly UAI 15.795.5 Lands Records: Eastern lands (Maine), unbound supplement, 1801-1803
These materials are not yet listed in the finding aid; they are severely mold-damaged and unavailable to researchers pending conservation treatment.